adelaide.edu.au 2019-12-07

# Privacy Statement | Legal Notices | University of Adelaide

This Privacy Statement informs visitors to our website about the type of information that may be collected about them and their browsing activity when they visit University of Adelaide webpages and how the information is used.

This website is administered by the University of Adelaide.

Expand
  * ## Cookies

To improve your experience on our site, we may use cookies. A cookie is a packet of data that a website places on your computer to identify you as a visitor to that website and remember your preferences. Cookies do not contain personally identifying information about you.

You may refuse the use of cookies by changing the settings on your web browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

  * ## Server logs and website analytics

When you access the University of Adelaide's website, our server may log the following information:

    * Your browser's Internet address
    * The date and time of your visit to the website
    * The pages you accessed and documents downloaded
    * The authentication credentials entered by you if accessing a restricted site or application.

Our website also uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers located outside Australia. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.

We use reports provided by Google Analytics and information logged by our server to help us understand our website traffic and usage, to gather statistics about how our web content is used and to maintain and improve our website service for users. We do not attempt to identify individuals as part of our regular business practices however in the event of an investigation, we may be required to inspect our server's logs or provide access to a law enforcement agency or other government agency with relevant legal authority.

By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in [Google's Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the [opt-out service](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) provided by Google.

  * ## Re-targeting

The University may use re-targeting to reach people who previously visited our website, to match the right advertisement to the right person. Google, Facebook and other internet based advertising companies serve our advertisements across the internet. These third parties use the cookies from users' browsers to serve advertisements based on the user's web preferences and usage patterns. If you have a cookie from our website stored on your computer, you may see our advertisements as you browse other sites.

If you would like to know more or opt out from third parties' use of cookies to serve you advertising messages, please visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) website. If you click this link, please be patient while the website generates the list of vendors who are using cookies on your browser.

If you have concerns about the University's use of re-targeting, please email [mc@adelaide.edu.au](mailto:mc@adelaide.edu.au).

  * ## Privacy information

Some of our online forms may require you to provide contact details and other personal information. We require these details in order to process and respond to your request, and for the general purposes set out in the [University’s Privacy Policy and Management Plan](http://www.adelaide.edu.au/policies/62/). If we intend to use the information for other purposes, these will be stated on the form.

Personal information collected by the University will be stored and used in accordance with the [University's Privacy Policy and Management Plan](http://www.adelaide.edu.au/policies/62/).

  * ## Hyperlinks

External sites that are linked from the University of Adelaide's website are generally not under our control or responsibility and you are advised to inform yourself of the privacy statements of those external sites.
